Contact

7398701500 (Mobile) sushrutmishra27@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sushrutkumar-mishra-10293a188 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language) SQL

Web Content Writing

Certifications

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing
Digital Skills: Web Analytics
Introduction to the Internet of Things
and Embedded Systems
Database Management System
Introduction to IOT

Sushrut Kumar Mishra

Technocrat || Final Year Noida

Summary

I am a Computer Science Undergrad in my last year of engineering. I am a motivated and eager-to-learn student with experience in programming technologies like Python, C, HTML5/CSS3, etc. I know Database technology MySQL. Currently, I am learning application framework Django.

Apart from academics, I work as a content writer in my free time. I have an eternal love for Traveling and Singing. I love to work voluntarily for social causes too.

Experience

Vardhan Consulting Engineers Summer Intern June 2020 - July 2020 (2 months)

YT&T

Web Content Writer
June 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

Education

Noida Institute of Engineering & Technology
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Kendriya vidyalaya Senior Secondary School · (2015 - 2017)